#### Contact

Iran, Qazvin Proivince, Qazvin City +98 9396988720 (Mobile) karimiashkan8181.pv@gmail.c om

www.linkedin.com/in/ashkankarimi-65a298261 (LinkedIn) github.com/ashkan-k (Other)

#### Top Skills

Django Laravel REST APIs

# Ashkan Karimi

Web Developer at PersiaWeb Qazvin Province, Iran

### Summary

Development of web software, mastery of Laravel framework and packaging (Laravel-Packaging) in Laravel and advanced topics of OOP and CLEAN CODE and relative mastery of PHP language and ability to create api and mastery of Ajax and spa with vue 2 and vue 3 and its sub-set frameworks, including vuetify, quasar, familiar with sockets in Laravel (Pusher), familiar with sockets in Django (Channels), familiarity with Golang, familiarity with Angular JS, database (Mysql, PosgreSQL), SQL commands, working experience with C# and Python and Django framework and django restframework, creating REST API, working experience with Ruby language, working experience in web penetration testing (slq, rfu, lfi, rce bugs) and testing tools Web penetration with Python, Laravel and Django testing, familiarization with vps configuration topics (nginx, apache, DB, vpn...)

Ready to learn new topics and extremely enthusiastic in his field of work

Laravel and Django sample codes (public) = https://github.com/ashkan-k/sample\_codes

Currently studying associate/bachelor's degree in computer software at Shahid Babaei Technical Vocational University of Qazvin.

I live in Qazvin, but I have the desire to work remotely in all cities.

## Experience

Persia Web Laravel Developer August 2023 - August 2024 (1 year 1 month) Isfahan Province, Iran

#### **CPOL**

Web Developer

September 2021 - September 2022 (1 year 1 month)

Isfahan Province, Iran

Kasboom

Web Developer

January 2020 - April 2020 (4 months)

Qazvin Province, Iran

## Education

Shahid Babaee Qazvin

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Software Engineering · (October 2021)

Zakaria Razi School

diploma, Computer Software Engineering · (October 2018 - May 2020)